Thorton Hall 912, 1600 Holloway Ave, San Francisco, CA 94132 1 (415) 767-8984

m.cadier.kim@gmail.com

ABOUT ME

I am a current graduate student in mathematics and researcher in machine learning. I have over four years of teaching experience from being a principal instructor of college math classes to one-on-one mentoring with high school students. I strive to have a dynamic, accessible, but consistently challenging approach to evangelizing mathematics.

WORK HISTORY

Machine Vision Engineer: UCSF Proctor Foundation in San Francisco, CA.

May, 2015 - present

Lecturer in Mathematics : San Francisco State University in San Francisco,

CA. September, 2014 - December, 2015

Data Scientist: Argyle Data in San Mateo, CA. June, 2014 - February, 2015

Papers

A Characterization of Generalized Permutohedra for the Classical Reflection Groups, 2015, (thesis)

Discriminating Eyelids with Trachomatous Inflammation - Follicular, with Dr. Travis Porco and Dr. Kazunori Okada, 2015, (in progress)

Conferences

Summer Graduate School on Geometric Group Theory at MSRI, Berkeley, CA, USA, 2015: invited participant

Fourth Encuentro Colombiano de Combinatoria at Universidad de los Andes, Bo-

gota, Colombia, 2014: invited speaker

FPSAC at KAIST, Daejeon, South Korea, 2015: participant

Richard Stanley Birthday Conference at MIT, Cambridge MA, USA, 2014: partic-

ipant

EDUCATION SFSU: MA, Mathematics, 2015

SFSU: BA, Philosophy, Mathematics, Computer Science, 2012

University of Paris 1 Pantheon la Sorbonne: Visiting Student, Philosophy,

Logic, Mathematics, 2009-2011

Teaching Math 60: Algebra I: fall , 2012 at SFSU

Math 70: Algebra II: summer , 2013 at SFSU

Math 60: Algebra I: fall, 2015 at SFSU Math 70: Algebra: fall, 2015 at SFSU

Math 199: Precalculus: fall, 2015 at SFSU

Languages/ Tools English French (Fluent) Java Python Matlab Julia C++

REFERNCES

Dr. David Bao, dbao@sfsu.edu, Chair of Math Dept. Addie Evans, addieevans@gmail.com, Teaching supervisor

Dr. Federico Ardila, federico@sfsu.edu, Academic Advisor Dr. Travis Porco, Travis.Porco@ucsf.edu, Research Supervisor